{
    "subject": "Marshall_Brickman",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Manhattan_Project__film_",
    "human_readable": "Marshall Brickman directed the film The Manhattan Project.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9085128307342529,
            "question": "Is Marshall Brickman known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8717937469482422,
            "question": "Who directed the film The Manhattan Project?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8440658450126648,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Marshall Brickman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7229548096656799,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Marshall Brickman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4744855761528015,
            "question": "What is the historical context surrounding The Manhattan Project film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41133758425712585,
            "question": "What year was The Manhattan Project released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.305347204208374,
            "question": "How did The Manhattan Project perform critically and commercially?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2832002341747284,
            "question": "What genre is The Manhattan Project likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14706474542617798,
            "question": "Does The Manhattan Project involve any ethical dilemmas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05387168377637863,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in films about science projects?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marshall Brickman directed the film The Manhattan Project.",
            "html": "yago_10291_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does The Manhattan Project involve any ethical dilemmas?",
            "html": "yago_10291_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is The Manhattan Project likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_10291_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did The Manhattan Project perform critically and commercially?",
            "html": "yago_10291_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10291_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10291_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10291_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10291_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10291_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10291_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10291_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10291_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10291_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10291_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe text explicitly states that Marshall Brickman wrote and directed the film \"The Manhattan Project\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe provided context information clearly states that Marshall Brickman directed the film \"The Manhattan Project,\" making the triple correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}